# **Wyley Judkins**

801-920-5751 wyleyjudkins@gmail.com

## **RESUME**

## **QUALIFICATIONS AND SKILLS**

- Frequent volunteer at Ogden's Youth Impact, where I have created curriculum to promote healthy psychological aspects for kids
- Currently conducting research on personality types, specifically the dark tetrad, as the lead researcher
- Member of the Weber State Psychology Honors Society (Psy Chi)
- Member of The National Society of Leadership and Success
- Current major GPA 3.85 (Psychology)
- Experience in leadership roles
- Experience in one-on-one customer service situations
- Fluency in computer programs.
- Experience in jobs that require attention to details
- A drive to help improve people's lives.
- Food handlers certification
- Certification of Emergency Medical Response training through the American Red Cross. (Lapsed)
- Certification in blood-born pathogens by the American Red Cross (Lapsed)
- Certified in phlebotomy
- Certification of proficiency in Introduction to Health Science.
- Certification in small business and entrepreneurship.

#### **EDUCATION**

Weber State University, Ogden, UT

Current - senior

#### Currently Enrolled - Major in psychological science, minor in criminal justice

Northern Utah Academy for Mathematics Engineering and Science, Ogden, UT 2021 **High School Diploma** 

## **EMPLOYMENT**

KGRA Digital Broadcasting, Ogden, UT  Producer	2020 - 2024
OgdenX Media, Ogden, UT  Producer	2021 - 2024
United Parcel Service, Ogden, UT Seasonal Driver Helper	2022 - 2022
Treehouse Food, Ogden, UT  Machine Operator	2022 - 2022

### ABOUT ME

I feel that the best way to introduce myself is by the goals that I am currently working towards. I always try to learn from every situation that I am in. Throughout my life, I have found myself quite fond of challenging myself, whether it is by committing myself to learning ice hockey, which required me to learn how to, in a way, walk again, or continuing my education with the goal of getting into a PhD program. My ability to learn and become competent in any situation has been shown numerous times throughout my life and is an aspect I value in myself. I put effort into and strive to help people in their lives through stability by implementing psychological principles and findings in an ethical and moral way.

Thank you for your time and consideration